My attempt to infiltrate Libelle Castle failed due to
an unexpected encounter with Her Highness,
the Princess Ashuna.
And during the scuffle,
Akari had disappeared off somewhere.
Meanwhile, Momo uncovered proof that Manon Libelle
was involved in the production of monstrine,
but fell into an enemy trap that left her critically injured.
Invoke
[Explosion]
Thanks to the proof Momo found,
the knights have taken action to sequester Libelle Island.
The time has come to confront Manon Libelle.
Around the same time,
I was in my true state that
Menou doesn't know about,
face-to-face with Miss Manon.
I have to figure out...
Why so many things are happening now in Libelle
that never took place in my past regressions.
Aren't you scared?
Because you've suspended these people in time?
No, not scared.
More importantly,
isn't there something you want to ask me?
So? Go ahead.
What is it you want to ask so badly that it
was worth leaving Miss Menou's side?
Last night, I snuck into your room to investigate...
But, it didn't help me figure anything out.
How do you know about me?
Because someone told me...
That you made the world Regress.
And not just once or twice either, I take it?
Who told you that?
Pandæmonium.
Episode 10:
The Daughter of a Lost One
Manon Libelle...
She may be more trouble than I expected.
"Pandemonium"? You mean that fog?
A confinement of fog that has lasted a thousand years...
Would you believe me if I told you I dispelled it?
What?
I don't think that's possible.
Indeed.
It's not something the likes of me
could ever do anything about.
I'm not looking to answer riddles, okay?
I've regressed countless times,
but none of this ever happened in Libelle before.
You changed something, didn't you?
In order to take revenge for your mom.
Revenge for my mother?
I heard these people talking.
They said this only happened
because you wanted vengeance.
It sounds like there's a slight misunderstanding,
so let me explain.
To tell you the truth, my mother was a Lost One.
Then she was Japanese?
Yes...
But unlike you, she wasn't summoned by anyone.
She was guided here by the stars,
a "lost one" in the truest sense.
I'm told the Fourth in this city were overjoyed at the time.
They had managed to secure someone with a
Pure Concept outside of the Faust's knowledge.
As the representative of the Fourth,
my father Count Libelle married the Lost One,
in order to keep her by his
side and make use of her power.
However, my father didn't make my mother use her
power, not even once.
Because at some point,
he had truly fallen in love with her.
As you must know...
The more a Lost One uses her power,
the more she loses her memories.
That was what my father was afraid of.
That my mother would forget
the time they spent together.
A beautiful story, isn't it?
But you know,
stories like that always come with a cruel ending.
Manon...
You actually have an older sister, you know.
A bright, active girl who's full of energy...
M-Mother...?!
Etheric Connect
Hold that in like your life depends on it, Lost One.
If you invoke that, your child will die.
Roughly ten years ago,
my mother was murdered by an
Executioner who came here: Flare.
That's your revenge?
Because Menou is the apprentice
of the one who killed your mom?
No.
I loved my mother,
but I understand the Church's reasoning that
otherworlders' Pure Concepts are dangerous.
They had reason enough to kill her.
So if it's revenge I'm after, I suppose it's against them.
My father convinced the Fourth not to worry,
because I would inherit my
mother's power in her stead.
So that my mother wouldn't have to use her power.
But I turned out to be an ordinary person,
and never inherited a Pure Concept.
What did I tell you?
I was told time and time again...
We should have... from the beginning!
that I was "a letdown"
and "worthless."
So of course that twisted my personality.
That's why I wanted to become taboo...
Exactly like they expected of me.
There's no point in trying anything.
Anyone suspended with my power
is shielded from external forces, so-
I want to live up to their expectations,
and prove just how idiotic those expectations were.
I'm in my rebellious phase, you see.
I think I'm starting to understand.
You... or the you in this instance of Time,
obtained a way to do that.
That's why the happenings in
Libelle changed drastically.
Chaos
I was powerless as my ordinary self.
That's why I will now become taboo!
Ether: Living Sacrifice - Chaos Adhesion,
Pure Concept [Chaos] - Summon [I Spy a Little Shadow]
I thought so. This power is stronger than yours.
How...?
That's right! There was one exception.
One thing my magecraft failed to stop.
That white globule I saw in Garm's ceremonial hall.
Then her power is on par with that?
It seems you're out of time.
Menou?!
M... Menou...
Oh... this... isn't... D-Don't think I'm being weird...
I just...
Wh-what do I do?
I showed myself in this state to Menou...
I'm sorry.
It was my mistake for letting you out of my sight.
I have a bunch of questions, but that can wait.
O-okay.
Hurry and get off this island.
There are some knights keeping watch,
so ask them to get Pastor Sicilia for you.
Understand?
What about you, Menou?
I'm going to go apprehend Manon Libelle.
My...
How nice of you to come out of your way.
I bid you welcome, Miss Menou.
Manon Libelle, you've stepped into the realm of taboo.
For that I must execute you.
Oh, this is lovely, Miss Menou.
It's clear to me now that you've said that.
As of now, I've truly become free and independent.
I will rebel against this world...
with this power I wield!
I embody the Fourth,
who seek to liberate the world in the
name of freedom and independence!
I have become what the Fourth is truly meant to be!
Hold on!
Please kill me as well, just like my mother!
Excuse me?
Why should I have to kill a little brat like you?
I'm the child of my mother, a Lost One!
I must have some power-
You don't.
Pure Concepts adhere to the soul.
And a soul, unlike the body,
is not genetic in the slightest.
It belongs solely to the individual born with it.
In short, you're not taboo.
I am taboo.
Come, Miss Menou.
Let us fight to our hearts' content.
She stood me up, hmm?
Though I find it hard to believe that Momo
would do this without good reason.
Princess Ashuna!
Didn't I tell you to let me be unless it's an emergency?
Some of the Fourth have turned themselves in,
and there's a high-ranking one among them.
Is it Manon Libelle?
No, an elderly man.
Probably one of the original members.
I see.
Then I'll go with you.
How lovely, Miss Menou.
Those eyes... I can't get enough of them...
It's over.
Invoke
[Gale]
Oh, my...
I win.
Well, this is as good as I can do...
But, it was so much better than
continuing to do nothing with my life.
This has been fun, Miss Menou.
It wasn't fun for me.
I see...
You don't like killing people, do you?
These roles in life, they're reprehensible, aren't they?
That's exactly why,
when trying to break free of restraints,
the people in this world turn to things that are taboo.
And you think that justifies you becoming taboo?
Of course not.
All I want to say...
is that you're allowed to change too, Miss Menou.
Like anyone else,
you have the right to rebel against the world.
If you wished it of her,
I'm sure Miss Akari would be happy
to use her powers for you.
Don't you dare say that!
You're surprisingly transparent.
But she said "countless times,"
so perhaps it's you who should be helping her change.
What are you talking about?
It's my policy not to divulge another girl's secrets.
Miss Menou, you've come after the wrong person.
You can come out now.
Ether: Living Sacrifice - Chaos Adhesion,
Pure Concept [Chaos] - Summon [Happy Birthday to Me]
Let me be the final sacrifice I offer you.
There's nothing you could have done... Miss Menou.
Things were already set in motion
long before you got here.
The only reason I was able to produce
monstrine was thanks to this girl.
Best of luck, Miss Menou.
Unlike me, she's more than just a handful.
I'm glad to see you're safe, Ms. Akari.
I'm sorry to have worried you.
It's fine.
We'll shelter you at the church.
Please come with me.
All right.
Maa! The sky is so blue. And big!
It's such nice weather today!
I'm sure it's going to be a lovely day.
Right? Don't you think so, too?
You worked so hard for me!
Thanks for providing me with a
decent number of sacrifices.
Hello there, Miss!
Meeting new people is one of my favorite things!
Is she using her own death as the
sacrifice required to summon herself?
If so, in a different sense from Akari,
she can't be killed.
You must be a priestess!
Is the girl with the cherry blossom pink hair okay?
I hope she's fine and didn't succumb to the poison!
I don't suppose you're a demon
summoned by Manon Libelle?
Of course not!
I'm human!
From the top of my head to the tips of my toes!
Yes...
You probably are human, technically.
This impossibly vile conjuring is
definitely that of a Pure Concept.
An entity that crossed the line as a Lost One...
The most taboo of taboos...
A Human Error.
Must I repeat myself again?!
We were all forced to do Manon Libelle's bidding!
We are the victims here!
"Forced to," eh?
It's true!
The girl even laced our council's food with monstrine!
With monstrine?
A Human Error.
The remnant of what was once a Lost One.
The worst monster imaginable.
That's awful! Don't call me a monster!
You know, I did a bunch of practice inside that
girl and finally learned how to talk again!
So I want to chat some more!
The things I love more than anything are
singing and dancing and watching movies!
I have no time for that.
Because my job is to kill entities like you.
Kill who? Me?
Yes, I'm going to destroy it.
Your Pure Concept, that is.
That's my meaning in life, after all.
Maa! Maa, you'll "destroy it"? My Pure Concept?!
Wow, amazing!
Oh. But it's true I'm super weak and I die really easily.
Still, you can't.
I mean, not even the Ivory hero managed to destroy me.
"Ivory hero"?
Maa! You don't know?!
But it was so amazing!
The strongest, greatest Pure Concept
ever in all of humankind!
A hero who was forced into protecting this stupid world!
But no one remembers?
When the hero did so much for the world?
That's why I think I remember hating you all.
Hate us for all I care.
I haven't met someone like you in a long time!
Thank you for coming on this wonderful day, everyone.
I welcome you to beat, crush,
and mash me up as you see fit.
There's more than enough of me so don't hold back.
Cast your inhibitions aside!
What you're about to witness is a B movie screening.
The entertainment of gods and
demons determined by dice!
Demons! Monsters! Dark Lords!
Mysterious wonders both divine and demonic.
The dice are governed by chance.
Who knows what will happen next?!
Ether: Living Sacrifice - Chaos Adhesion,
Pure Concept [Chaos] - Summon [Can I Call a Hundred Friends?]
I sense a conjuring!
It's so massive... and twisted.
Sacrificed... because of the monstrine?
Fear, excitement, and thrills-the triple package!
The singing, dancing,
embodiment of the panic film genre!
That's me, "Pandæmonium"!
Come on, let's have a riveting, enthralling,
and very fun fight to the death...
...Miss!
Next Episode
Pandæmonium
Next episode: Pandæmonium.